Liam Stout

Github/website

liamstout.com

liamstout221@gmail.com 07544556414

INTRO

Since 2017 I have been writing python scripts and building websites. Over the last 2 years I began to take it more seriously and was learning new things everyday. As I learnt more I began applying and eventually I landed my first job as a web developer at Monmia.

HTML
CSS/SASS
Javascript
Nodejs
React Native
Git
Python

Everyday I am learning new things and expanding my field of knowledge in programing and developing applications. While strengthening existing skills I look to learn new skills to progress my career. On my website you can see examples of my work.

EXPERIENCE

The Original Factory Shop | Sales Assistant

October 2017 - January 2020

As a sales assistant at the original factory shop I have gained valuable experience in customer service. Providing customers a service in a polite and efficient manner is a vital part of the job. Making sure the store is tidy and full is also important in the role along with handling cash and other payment methods.

Monmia | Web Developer

January 2020 - PRESENT

Monmia was my first time as a developer in a professional environment because of this I Learn new things everyday on ways to improve the way I work alongside with the help of more experienced colleagues. At Monmia my role was to maintain and expand upon an existing React application. Alongside this I dabbled in salesforce and other tools used in a commercial environment.

Chime | Android/IOS Development

PRESENIT

More recently I have also been helping out on a react-native project by building out new screens and features giving me experience in mobile development.

EDUCATION

Sir Harry Smith Community College | GCSE

September 2012 - June 2017 In my GCSEs I achieved a English 4 - Maths 4

Graphic Design C - Sociology C - ECDL Distinction*

Peterborough Regional College | BTEC

September 2017 - June 2019

During my 2 years at PRC I left with a MPP in Digital Media Production (Film/TV/Radio) at a Level 3 full diploma standard.

SKILLS

Hardworking

Self-motivated

Punctual

Self teach

Good Communication

REFERENCES

Available upon request.